A Guide to the Near East Foundation records Accessions 2009.104, 2010.002, 2010.020 FA406
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2009.104: Near East Foundation records, 1915-2003; 1940-1980; AC 2009:104; 180 Cubic Feet 168 boxes, including 150 standard record storage boxes
  - Personnel/Contracts
    - Abbey, Robert L. (Box 99)
    - Adok, Robert L. (Box 99)
    - Personal - Dr. Robert E. Adock - Ghana, 1972 August (Box 99)
    - A. Antoniadou (Box 99)
    - Souad Ajlani - Personal, 1956 (Box 99)
    - Sou Ajlani - Personal, 1954-1955 (Box 99)
    - Personal - Ulverd U. Alexander - Africa (Box 99)
    - Alexander, Ulverd U. - Contract (Box 99)
    - Personal - Harold B. Allen (Box 99)
    - Paul H. Allen (Box 99)
    - Personnel - Rutillus H. Allen (Box 99)
    - Allen, Rutillus H. (Box 99)
    - Personnel - Anderson, C. David (Box 99)
    - Personal - Allen, Theodore W. - Iran (Box 99)
    - Contract - Allen, T.W. - Iran (Box 99)
    - Alonzo, Alicia A. (Box 99)
    - Contract - Victor F. Amann (Box 99)
    - Victor F. Amann- Botswana (Box 99)
    - Contract - Ambrose, Frederic A. - Africa Agric. & Edu. Advisor (Box 99)
    - Personal - Ambrose, Frederic A. - Africa Agri. & Edu. Advisor (Box 99)
    - Pesonnel - Phoebus Anastassiades (Box 99)
    - Andresen, Andrew J., Jr. - Agronomy, Soils, Conservation (Box 99)
    - Contract - Andresen, Andrew J. (Box 99)
    - C. David Anderson (Box 99)
    - Contract - Anderson, C. David (Box 99)
    - Nelson C. Anderson - Botswana, 1976 (Box 99)
    - Conract - Nelson C. Anderson (Box 99)
    - Nelson C. Anderson (Box 100)
    - Contract - Anderson, Nelson C. - Africa Agricult. Extension Advisor (Box 100)
    - Contract - Anderson, Sanford M. (Box 100)
    - Anderson, Sanford M. - Mali (Box 100)
    - Anderson, Sanford M. (Box 100)
    - Contract - Sanford M. Anderson (Box 100)
    - Anderson, Sanford M., 1976 (Box 100)
    - Personnel - Andrew, Louis (Box 100)
    - Contact - Andrew, Louis (Box 100)
    - Anthony, Frank - Contract (Box 100)
    - Personnel - Araventino, Calliope (Box 100)
    - A. David Arfa (Box 100)
    - Arfa, A. David (Box 100)
    - Contract - David Arfa (Box 100)
    - Aro, Richard S. (Box 100)
    - Contract - Richard S. Aro (Box 100)
    - Contract - Aro, David S., Ph.D. (Box 100)
    - Aro, Richard S., Ph.D. - Rnage Manag. & Research (Box 100)
    - Agrarian - Ashbury, Fuhrman - Community Development Specialist (Box 100)
    - Aughenbaugh, Wm. A. - Contract (Box 100)
    - Personal - William A. Aughenbaugh, 1968 (Box 100)
    - Axtell, Bryan, Ph.D. - Personal (Box 100)
    - Contract - Axtell, Bryan (Dr.) (Box 100)
    - Personnel - "B" General (Box 100)
    - Behjat Badamchian - Lesotho (Box 100)
    - Personal - W. Kenneth Bach - Libya (Box 100)
    - Personal - Gail A. Bagley - Africa, 1966 (Box 100)
    - Contract - G.A. Bagley - Tanzania (Box 100)
    - Banks, Bonnie Ruth (Box 100)
    - Personnel - Barnes, Glann J. (Box 100)
    - Conract - Barnes, Glenn J. (Box 100)
    - Alexander Bartosik (Box 101)
    - Bartolo, Robert H. - Kenya (Box 101)
    - Contract - Bartolo, Robert H. (Box 101)
    - Basnight, Leronia (Box 101)
    - Alpha - Ethel S. Beer (Willms) (Box 101)
    - Alpha - Iris Deras - Greece (Box 101)
    - Alpha - Willms' Memorial - Corresp. Mrs. Mayyasi (Box 101)
    - Willms Memorial - Misc. (Box 101)
    - Miss Emilie Willms Memorial Fund (Box 101)
    - Miss Emilie Willms' Memorial Fund (Box 101)
    - Personnel - Beers, N. Mason (Box 101)
    - Contract - Beers, Newell Mason (Box 101)
    - Personnel - Bell, Theodore L. - Iran, 1964 (Box 101)
    - Contract - Bell, Theodore L. - Iran, 1962 (Box 101)
    - Mr. Robert Benda - Claim File - INA, Health Insurance Proof of Loss Form (Box 101)
    - Contract - Benda, Robert S. (Box 101)
    - Benda, Robert S. - Kenya (Box 101)
    - Personnel - Berlin, Jacob B. (Box 101)
    - Jacob B. Berlin (Box 101)
    - Agrarian - Bertsch, Howard - Senior Rural Credit Specialist (Box 101)
    - Personnel - Bertsch, Howard (Box 101)
    - Contract - Birky, Carl W. (Box 101)
    - Personnel - Birky, Carl W. (Box 101)
    - Personnel - Birky, Pauline E. (Mrs. Carl Birky) (Box 101)
    - Contract - Birky, Pauline (Mrs. Carl) (Box 101)
    - Personnel - Blumberg, Leonard John (Box 101)
    - Contract - Blumberg, Leonard John (Box 101)
    - Contract - Cecil T. Blunn (Box 102)
    - Personal - Cecil t. Blunn (Box 102)
    - Gary Bond - Botswana (Box 102)
    - Bonnema, Pieter J. - Personal Conservation Officer of Operations (Box 102)
    - Booth, Robert E. - Tanzania (Box 102)
    - Contract - Booth, Robert E. (Box 102)
    - Eric T. Boulter - Contract (Box 102)
    - Denis S. Bower (Box 102)
    - Margaret Anne Bower (Box 102)
    - Contract - Bracken, (Joy) Dolores (Box 102)
    - Personnel - Bracken, Dolores (Box 102)
    - Bredemeier, Lorenz F. - Lesotho (Box 102)
    - Contract - Bredemeier, Lorenz F. (Box 102)
    - Contract - Briesemeister, Ethel (Box 102)
    - Brink, Burnell W. (Box 102)
    - Personnel - Broome, Dr. Edwin C. (Box 102)
    - Personal - Donald C. Brown, 1969 (Box 102)
    - Brown, Donald C. - Contract (Box 102)
    - Herbert F. Brownlee - Nigeria (Box 102)
    - Nigeria - Herbert Brownlee - Personal File (Box 102)
    - William A. Broyles (Box 102)
    - Personnel - Bruner, John (Box 102)
    - Personal - Dr. Henry Burnner (Box 102)
    - Dr. Brunner (Box 102)
    - Contract - Dr. L.G. Buchan (Box 102)
    - Thomas Bunch (Box 102)
    - Personnel - Thomas R. Bunch - Contract - Mali (Box 102)
    - Personnel - Susan E. Burke (Box 102)
    - Contract - Susan E. Burke, 1973 (Box 102)
    - Personal - Robert H. Burns - Iran, 1967 December (Box 102)
    - Personal - Robert H. Burns - Iran, 1968 January (Box 103)
    - Contract - Burns, Robert H. (Dr.) Ahwaz (Box 103)
    - Personnel - Burns, Samuel (Box 103)
    - Contract - Burns, Samuel Lee (Box 103)
    - Robert H. Burns (Box 103)
    - Bruce Butterfield - Bhutan (Box 103)
    - Bhutan - Bruce Butterfield - Personal File (Box 103)
    - Personnel - "C" General (Box 103)
    - Personal - Cecil M. Cannon - Africa - Well Driller - Madagascar (Box 103)
    - Cannon, Cecil M. - Contract (Box 103)
    - Personnel - Cannon, David R. (Box 103)
    - Contract - Cannon, David R. (Box 103)
    - Carmichael, Gregory M. - Sanitation Engineer, 1977 October (Box 103)
    - Personnel - Carpenter, Maurice Dean (Box 103)
    - Contract - Carpenter, Maurice Dean, 1954 (Box 103)
    - Alice G. Carr - Confidential (Box 103)
    - Carroll, Paul H. - Lesotho (Box 103)
    - Personnel - Casella, Jean, 1955 (Box 103)
    - Cassile, Helen H. (Box 103)
    - Cerny, James N. - Tanzania (Box 103)
    - Contract - Cerny, James N. (Box 103)
    - Judy Chestnutt (Box 103)
    - Contract - Christiansen, James E. - Iran (Box 103)
    - Personnel - Christiansen, James E. - Iran (Box 103)
    - Contract - Dr. Howard Christensen - Iran, 1972 August (Box 103)
    - Personal - Dr. Howard Christensen- Iran, 1972 August (Box 103)
    - Contract - Nephi A. Christensen, 1968, 1970 (Box 103)
    - Dr. Nephi Albert Christensen (Box 103)
    - Personal - Nephi A. Christensen - Iran (Box 103)
    - Personal - Andrew Clark - Tanzania (Box 103)
    - Contract - Andrew A. Clark, 1971 (Box 104)
    - Contract - Andrew A. Clark - Africa, 1967 (Box 104)
    - Personal - Andrew A. Clark (Box 104)
    - Mr. R. L. Clark (Box 104)
    - Clark, Ross L. - Contract (Box 104)
    - Personal - Clayton, Leon C. - Africa - Agriculture Advisor - Team Leader (Box 104)
    - Contract - Clayton, Leon C. - Africa - Agriculture Advisor - Team Leader (Box 104)
    - Mr. William Z. Cline - Personnel (Box 104)
    - Contract - Cobb, Walter R. (Box 104)
    - Personnel - Cobb, Walter R. (Box 104)
    - Contract - Coe, Edwin D. (Box 104)
    - Coe, Edwin D. - Botswana (Box 104)
    - Contract - Cooper, Harold W. (Box 104)
    - Cooper, Harold W. - Lesotho (Box 104)
    - Contract - Mrs. Hilda W. Cooper (Box 104)
    - Cornett, Elgin - Project Coordinator, 1975 (Box 104)
    - Contract - Elgin M. Cornett - Africa, 1967 (Box 104)
    - Crawford, Martha Hamilton - Contract (Box 104)
    - Crossley, Geoffrey - Lesotho (Box 104)
    - Contract - Crossley, Geoffrey (Box 104)
    - Personnel - Crowther, C.I. (Box 104)
    - Crowther, Cyril I. (Deceased) Claim File - Aetna Life Claim - Death Certificate (Box 104)
    - Personnel - "D" General (Box 104)
    - Personnel - Daggett, Earl B. (Box 104)
    - Contract - Daggett, Earl B. (Box 104)
    - Daniel, Eddie F. - Ethiopia (Box 104)
    - Contract - Daniel, Eddie F. (Box 104)
    - Mr. George M. Danielson - Claim File Medical Receipts, 1978 (Box 104)
    - Danielson, George M. - Lesotho (Box 104)
    - Contract - Danielson, George M. (Box 104)
    - Personnel - Thomas C. Dassel (Box 104)
    - Contract - Thomas C. Dassel (Box 104)
    - Marjorie Davis - Contract (Box 104)
    - Deckelmann, W.B. - An. Science Dairy b.'27, 1974 (Box 104)
    - Personal - William B. Deckelmann - Africa, 1966-1970 (Box 105)
    - Deckelmann, William B. - Contract - Tanzania, 1968 (Box 105)
    - Personal - William B. Deckelmann, 1971 (Box 105)
    - Contract - William B. Deckelmann, 1971 (Box 105)
    - Personal - Scotty F. Deffendol - Chad, 1974 July (Box 105)
    - Personal - Scotty F. Deffendol, 1969-1971 (Box 105)
    - Deffendol, Scotty - Chad, 1971 (Box 105)
    - Contract - Deffendol, Scotty, 1976 (Box 105)
    - Contract - Scotty F. Deffendol, 1972 (Box 105)
    - Contract - Scotty F. Deffendol - Africa (Box 105)
    - Personnel - R.J. Dewey (Box 105)
    - Contract - Dewey, Robert John (Box 105)
    - Contract - Dickie, Alexander, IV (Box 105)
    - Alex Dickie - End of Tour - Masai Range Project - Tanzania, 1977-1979 (Box 105)
    - Dickie, Alex, Jr. - Range b.54, 1976 June (Box 105)
    - Mathias N. Dietrick - Contract (Box 105)
    - Dillon, Anna-Elizabeth - Claim (Box 105)
    - Peter L. Doan - Consultant (Box 105)
    - Rebecca Miles Doan (Box 105)
    - Dodd, Dr. Wilson F. - Contract (Box 105)
    - Dodd, Dr. Wilson F. - Personnel (Box 105)
    - Dodd, Robert H. - Swaziland, 1976 (Box 105)
    - Contract - Dodd, Robert H. (Box 105)
    - Dooley, Delmer J. (Box 105)
    - Delmer J. Dooley (Box 105)
    - Personnel - Doughty, William (Box 105)
    - Downes, Dr. R.E. - Personnel - Contract - Sociology & Anthropology (Box 105)
    - Contract - Dwight M. Dunbar (Box 105)
    - Dwight M. Dunbar - Kenya - Agricultural Statistician (Box 105)
    - Contract - Dunn, James F. (Box 105)
    - Dunn, James F. - Botswana (Box 105)
    - Personal - Dunn, Robert W.- Africa - Well Driller, Team Leader (Box 106)
    - Bhutan - Dunn, Robert - Personal (Box 106)
    - Robert W. Dunn - Bhutan (Box 106)
    - Contract - Dunn, Robert W. - Africa - Well Driller - Team Leader (Box 106)
    - Personnel - "E" General (Box 106)
    - Contract - Easter, Glenn (Box 106)
    - Easter, Glenn - Iran (Box 106)
    - Mrs. Loretta Egan - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 106)
    - Personal - Dr. A. Ekrami - Iran (Box 106)
    - Personal - H.D. Elijah - Tanzania (Box 106)
    - Contract - H.D. Elijah, 1971 (Box 106)
    - Liberia - William Elliot - Personal (Box 106)
    - William J. Elliot - Liberia (Box 106)
    - Personal - F.I. Elliott (Box 106)
    - Contract - Elliott, Irvine F. (Box 106)
    - Contract - Ellithorpe, Glenn D. (Box 106)
    - Ellithorpe, Glenn L. - Lesotho (Box 106)
    - Contract - Eng. Henry H. (Box 106)
    - Eng, Henry H. - Mechanical Maintenance (Box 106)
    - Personal - John C. Engle - Tanzania (Box 106)
    - T,O,21 - Engle, John E. - Accounting Teacher (Box 106)
    - Contract - John C. Engle (Box 106)
    - Engles, Scott R. - Tanzania (Box 106)
    - Contract - Engle, Scott R. (Box 107)
    - Mr. Gary Enright - Livestock Mktg. (Box 107)
    - Erickson, C. Telford (Box 107)
    - Eriksmoen, Duane Alan - Contract (Box 107)
    - Personal - Duane A. Eriksmoen - 1968 (Box 107)
    - Erickson, Kenneth A. (Marilyn, also) Financial Analyst - ADB (Box 107)
    - Contract - Ericksson, Sigurd (Box 107)
    - Ericksson, Sigurd - Iran (Box 107)
    - Africa Quarterly Progress Reports (Task Order #4) Niger (Box 106)
    - Niger - Seed Analysis - Rutgers University (Box 106)
    - Africa - Quarterly Report - T.O.#4- Niger, 1969. 1970 (Box 106)
    - Africa - Weber, Fred - Task Order #4 Niger, 1965 (Box 106)
    - Africa - Agricultural Extension Project - T.O.#6 - Cameroon (Box 106)
    - "Life in Cameroon" by Linda Williams (Box 106)
    - Africa - Literature - T.O.#6 Cameroon (Box 106)
    - Africa - Monthly Reports - Cameroon T.O. #6, 1969 (Box 106)
    - Africa - Monthly Reports - Cameroon T.O. #6, 1968 (Box 106)
    - Africa - Monthly Reports - Cameroon T.O. #6, 1966 (Box 106)
    - Africa - Monthly Reports - Cameroon T.O. #6, 1967 (Box 106)
    - Africa - Monthly Reports - Cameroon T.O. #6, 1965 (Box 106)
    - Africa - Office - T.O. #6 - Cameroon - Gen. Corresp. (Box 106)
    - Africa - Interim Progress Report by W.C. Putman- Upper Volta - T.O. #8 (Box 106)
    - Africa - Literature - T.O.#8 Upper Volta, 1965 (Box 106)
    - Africa - Monthly Reports - Upper Volta T.O.#8, 1969 (Box 106)
    - Upper Volta - Monthly Reports, 1970 (Box 106)
    - Africa - Monthly Reports - Upper Volta - T.O.#8, 1968 (Box 106)
    - Africa - Monthly Reports - Upper Volta - T.O.#8, 1964 (Box 106)
    - Africa - Monthly Reports - Upper Volta - T.O.#8, 1965 (Box 106)
    - Plan of Work by W.C. Putman - T.O.#8 - Upper Volta (Box 106)
    - Africa - Quarterly Report - T.O.#8 Upper Volta, 1969 (Box 106)
    - Africa - Quarterly Reports - T.O. #8 - Upper Volta, 1965-1968 (Box 106)
    - Africa - Water Resources Project T.O.#8 - Upper Volta, 1965 (Box 106)
    - Africa - Trip to Bobo-Dioulasso August 1965 by Warren C. Putman - T.O.#8 - Upper Volta, 1965 August (Box 106)
    - Africa - Van Voorthuizen, E.G. - T.O.#8 Upper Volta, 1965 (Box 106)
    - Africa - Office - General T.O.#9 Tanzania (Box 106)
    - Central Establishment - Tanzania (Box 106)
    - Government - A.I.D. General (Box 106)
    - Africa - Calendar of Work - T.O. #2 Dahomey, 1965 (Box 106)
    - Africa - Monthly Reports - Dahomey T.O. #2, 1969 (Box 106)
    - Africa - Monthly Reports - Dahomey T.O.#2, 1968 (Box 106)
    - Africa - Monthly Reports - T.O.#2 Dahomey, 1967 (Box 106)
    - Africa - Monthly Reports - T.O.#2 Dahomey, 1966 (Box 106)
    - Noe, T.H (Box 28)
  - Publications
    - Annual Report, 1965 (Box 91)
    - Annual Report, 1976 (Box 91)
    - Annual Report, 1964 (Box 91)
    - Annual Report, 1974 (Box 91)
    - Annual Report, 1972 (Box 91)
    - Annual Report, 1969 (Box 91)
    - Annual Report, 1961 (Box 91)
    - Annual Report, 1970 (Box 91)
    - Annual Report, 1975 (Box 91)
    - Annual Report, 1962 (Box 91)
    - What the NEF Needs Most from American is...the Gift of Skill (Box 91)
    - A Life of Helping Others to Help Themselves - Cleveland E. Dodge (Box 91)
    - NEF NEWS Vol. V111, No. 1 - Spring, 1972 (Box 91)
    - Near East Foundation NEWS Vol. IX No. 1 - Spring, 1973 (Box 91)
    - NEF NEWS Vol. V, No. 3 - Fall, 1969 (Box 91)
    - NEF NEWS Vol. IV. No. 1 - Spring, 1968 (Box 91)
    - NEF NEWS Vol.IV No. 2 - Fall, 1968 (Box 91)
    - NEF NEWS Vol.III No. 5 - Fall, 1967 (Box 91)
    - NEF NEWS Vol.V No. 2 - Spring, 1969 (Box 91)
    - NEF NEWS Vol.V No. 1 - Special Earthquake Issue, 1969 January-February (Box 91)
    - NEF NEWS Vol.VI No. 1 - Spring, 1970 (Box 91)
    - NEF NEWS Vol. VII No. 1 - Spring, 1971 (Box 91)
    - NEF NEWS Vol. VII, No. 2 Fall, 1971 (Box 91)
    - NEF News Vol. VIII, No. 2 - Fall, 1972 (Box 91)
    - NEF NEWS Vol. IX, No. 2 - Fall, 1973 (Box 91)
    - NEF NEWS Vol.X No. 1 - Spring, 1974 (Box 91)
    - NEF NEWS Vol. X No. 2 - Fall, 1974 (Box 91)
    - NEF NEWS Vol.XI No. 1 - Spring, 1975 (Box 91)
    - NEF NEWS Vol.XI No. 2 - Fall, 1975 (Box 91)
    - NEF NEWS Vol.XII No.1 - Spring, 1976 (Box 92)
    - NEF NEWS Vol. XII, No. 2 - Fall, 1976 (Box 92)
    - NEF NEWS Vol.XIII No. 1 - Spring, 1977 (Box 92)
    - NEF News, Vol. XIII, No. 2 - Fall, 1977 (Box 92)
    - NEF in Africa - Helping People to Help Themselves (Box 92)
    - Stop the Snail (Box 92)
    - NEF Gift Card draft board (Box 92)
    - NEF News Special Report (Box 92)
    - NEF - Helping People Help Themselves, 1982-1983 (Box 92)
    - The Way Up - NEF at Work in Underdeveloped Areas (Box 92)
    - Annual Report, 1963 (Box 92)
    - Annual Report, 1966 (Box 92)
    - Annual Report, 1968 (Box 92)
    - Annual Report, 1973 (Box 92)
    - What is...Near East Foundation (Box 92)
    - NEF - Introduction to the Near East Foundation (Box 92)
    - Nursing Service - A Vital Need in Lebanon Today (Box 92)
    - Annual Report, 1986 (Box 92)
    - Annual Report, 1985 (Box 92)
    - Annual Report, 1987 (Box 92)
    - Annual Report, 1988 (Box 92)
    - American N.E.F. patch, 2016:FA406:032 (Folder SF32)
    - Christmas Calendars through the years; Donation/Gift cards; Information cards (Box 93)
    - Annual Report, 1970 (Box 92)
    - Ideas for 1969 Annual Report & for Christmas Card (Box 92)
    - Annual Report, 1969 (Box 92)
    - Didge, Bayard - Princeton, NJ (Box 92)
    - Form Letters (Box 92)
    - Arlene Francis (Box 92)
    - NEF News - Spring, 1972 (Box 92)
    - Christmas Card, 1970 (Box 92)
    - Christmas Card, 1971 (Box 92)
    - Visa Forms (Box 92)
    - Mrs. Charles Victrey (Box 92)
    - Rockefeller, Mrs. Laurance (Box 92)
    - Preprau (Legal) (Box 92)
    - Copy for Fall 1971 Newspaper (Box 92)
    - NEF in Iran - film - script & correspondence (Box 92)
    - Newspapers (Box 92)
    - Spring Newspaper, 1971 (Box 92)
    - Appeals, 1984-1985 (Box 92)
    - "The Future of U.S. relationships with the Arab Nation" John S. Badeau (Box 92)
    - The Type of American Suitable for Work in the Middle East (Box 92)
    - Report to the Board of Directors of NEF on Trip to the Near East, H.B. Allen, Director of Programs, 1955 September 15 - 1956 January 14 (Box 92)
    - Extracts from the Report of the Director of Programs to the New York Office on his Tour of the Middle East, 1955 September 16 - 1956 January 14 (Box 92)
    - Consideration of and Proposal for Technical Assistance to Developing Countries of Africa (Box 92)
    - "JASH" Self-Help Program in Jordan - Progress Report, 1968 March (Box 92)
    - Report on Inspection & Review of NEF Work & Services in Africa to the Agency for International Development, 1966 December 30 (Box 92)
    - Report on Inspection & Review of NEF Work & Services in Africa to the Agency for international Development, 1966 February 24 (Box 92)
    - Present Situation & Development Potential for Vegetable & Other Food Crops in West Cameroon, 1967 January (Box 92)
    - Potential for Swine Production & Marketing in West Cameroon. By Charles H. Rust, 1966 December (Box 92)
    - Potential for Poultry in West Cameroon by Charles H. Rust, 1966 December (Box 92)
    - Livestock Survey of West Africa by Waren C. Putman, 1969 June 18 (Box 92)
    - A Handbook on Resource Conservation Lesotho Agricultural College, 1977 (Box 92)
    - Botswana Agricultural College - Syllabus for Certificate in Community Development Course (Box 92)
    - Tribal Grazing Land Policy - Senior Agricultural Officers' Workshop, 1976 November 15-19 (Box 92)
    - Botswana Agricultural College - Prospectus (Box 92)
    - Botswana Agricultural College - Handbook, 1976 (Box 92)
    - Completion of Assignment Report for the Period - by Richard L. Hurelbrink, 1976 August 23 - 1978 August 22 (Box 92)
    - Livestock & Range Research in Botswana, 1978 (Box 92)
    - Mathematical Modeling of Livestock Production Systems: Application of the Texas A&M University Beef Cattle Production Model to Botswana, 1978 (Box 92)
    - Report on Inspection & Review of NEF Work & Services in Africa, 1974 April 24 (Box 92)
    - A Proposal for the Expansion of the Animal Science Education Facilities of the University of Azarbaijan by Nephi A. Christensen, 1974 June 20 (Box 92)
    - Fifth Annual Report, 1974 August (Box 92)
    - C-193 T.O.#6 Cameroon - Special Rpt./Veg. & Other Food Crops (Box 94)
    - C-193 T.O.#6 Tour End - (Carlier & Larson) Cameroon, 1967-1969 (Box 94)
    - C-193 T.O.#6 Tour End Report - W.Cameroon (R. Williams), 1965-1967 (Box 94)
    - C-193 T.O.4 End of Tour Reports - Niger (Carlier), 1969 April - 1970 May (Box 94)
    - C-193 T.O.5 Tour End - Malagasy - C.C. Cannon, 1967-1969 (Box 94)
    - C-193 T.O.2 - Dahomey Tour End -J.W. Taylor, 1966 January - 1968 February (Box 94)
    - End of Tour on Pasture Development in Uganda - Calvin C. Merinar, 1973 June (Box 94)
      - Photos, 2016:FA406:033 (Folder SF33)
    - Unlabeled Folder (Box 94)
    - A Twentieth Century Concept of Practical Philanthropy (Box 126)
    - NEF A Brief Description of its Policies & Program, 1959 January 1st (Box 126)
    - NEF Annual report of the Foreign Director, 1941-1942 (Box 126)
    - NEF Annual Report of Director of Programs, 1954, 1956 (Box 126)
    - NEF Board of Dierctors Objectives & Policies Adopted (Revised May 17, 1972), 1968 April 24 (Box 126)
    - Specialized Personnel & Consultative Specialists of NEF, 1943 (Box 126)
    - Extracts from the Reports of the Directors of Program to the New York Office on His Tour of the Middle East, 1955 September 16 - 1956 January 14 (Box 126)
    - Report of the President - Overseas Inspection Trip, 1960 February 10-April 30 (Box 126)
    - Information to Assist OPEX Personnel, 1972 August (Box 126)
    - Manual of Area Operational Procedures (Box 126)
    - A Brief Statement of its Organization Objecctives, Financing, Program & Administration (Box 126)
    - NEF Principals & Policies of Operation, 1962 July 1 (Box 126)
    - Demonstrations & Technical Assistance, 1966 January (Box 126)
    - Suggested Criteria for Evaluating Certain Types of Technical Assistance Programs, 1966 (Box 126)
    - Integration the Ultimate Goal in Raising Standards of Living in Underdeveloped Areas - Experinece of NEF, 1966 January (Box 126)
    - The Types of American Suitable for work in the Middle East (Box 126)
    - Adapting Programs of Rural Improvement to Newly Developing Areas, 1966 (Box 126)
    - A Perspective on International Development by John F. Hilliard, 1967 (Box 126)
    - Near East Relief - Report to Congress, 1923 (Box 126)
    - Near East Relief - A Review for 1922 - Annual Report to Congress by Charles V. Vickrey, 1923 (Box 126)
    - The Goal We Seek in Technical Assistance for Under Developed Areas (Box 126)
    - The Near East Relief by James L. Barton, 1915-1930 (Box 126)
    - How Near East Foundation Operates - A Statement of Principles & Procedures, 1951 (Box 126)
    - Foundations for the Future - J. George Harrar, 1966 May 11 (Box 126)
    - Personnel Training for Reconstruction Service in the Near East, 1943 February 26 (Box 126)
    - Not a Handout...but a Helping Hand (Box 126)
    - Supporting Private Aid to Developing Countries - A Message to Corporate Executives with Interests Overseas (Box 126)
    - A Proposal for Teacher Education in Agricultural Iran by Henry S. Brunner, 1971 May (Box 126)
    - Education of the Small Farmer of the Less Developed Countries, 1978 March (Box 126)
    - Selection of Personnel for Overseas Assignments (Box 126)
    - Background & Policy Statement of NEF (Box 126)
    - NEF Board of Directors Objectives & Policies, 1972 (Box 126)
    - A Study Relating to the Promotion of Youth Clubs in Lebanon by Hanna Khouri, 1971 July (Box 126)
    - Personnel Policies & Practices, 1977 January (Box 126)
    - Health Precautions & Practices, 1977 (Box 126)
    - Information to Assist OPEX Personnel, 1975 June (Box 126)
    - Consideration of & Proposal for Technical Assistance to Developing Countries in Africa, 1972 (Box 126)
    - Design for Corporate Giving, 1964 December 9 (Box 126)
    - John Goelet (Box 126)
    - John Goelet (Box 126)
    - Greece - Rice Village Survey, 1951 (Box 126)
    - Bhutan (Box 126)